<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home, Weather on Summitt Dweller&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/Home-Weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home, Weather on Summitt Dweller&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/Home-Weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Iowa&#39;s 2020 Hurricane</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/iowas-2020-hurricane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/iowas-2020-hurricane/</guid>
      <description>It’s been far too long, again, since I posted to this blog, but this time I have a legitimate excuse: we’ve been without power or internet, or much of anything, since about 11:45 AM on Monday, August 10, 2020. So we have now been more than 10.5 days without power. I’m only able to post this because of a portable generator I bought on August 12 (that was an adventure in itself) and the wireless hotspot that my phone has provided almost 24/7 ever since the storm hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowpocalypse 2024 - Round 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/snowpocalypse-2024-round-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/snowpocalypse-2024-round-2/</guid>
      <description>Just thought I would post a couple more photos, with a probable update later today. Took these photos yesterday (Friday, January 12) at about noon when I ventured outside to clear the driveway. Didn&amp;rsquo;t quite get it all done because it was just too cold and windy, and the snow was still falling. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even attempt to clear the front porch&amp;hellip; ain&amp;rsquo;t nobody coming to visit today anyway. 8^) There are steps and a deck under there somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowpocalypse 2024?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/snowpocalypse-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/snowpocalypse-2024/</guid>
      <description>Maybe not as bad as predicted (at least per some predictions) but it was enough wet snow for me. Took almost an hour to clear using my EGO cordless snow-thrower (love it) and there&amp;rsquo;s more to be done before Mackenzie and I can leave for work in the morning. Fortunately both Grinnell College and South Tama County schools were closed today. GC re-opens at noon tomorrow and STC just announced that they will be closed on Wednesday too.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
